import '../Model/Question.Model.dart';

List<Questions> questionsList = [
  Questions(
      id: 0,
      answer: 0,
      question: 'A scrollable widget',
      options: ['ListView', 'Expanded', 'MaterialButton', 'Container']),
  Questions(id: 1, answer: 0, question: 'Flutter is a ?', options: [
    'framework',
    'programming language',
    'Application',
    'All of the above is true'
  ]),
  Questions(
      id: 2,
      answer: 1,
      question: 'Firebase is Presented by ?',
      options: ['Meta', 'Google', 'Amd', 'Microsoft']),
  Questions(
      id: 3,
      answer: 1,
      question: 'Fastest local storage',
      options: ['ShredPrefrence', 'Hive', 'SqFlite', 'GetStorage']),
  Questions(
      id: 4,
      answer: 2,
      question: 'An EcoSystem State Mangement',
      options: ['Provider', 'Bloc', 'Getx', 'None a bove is true']),
  Questions(
      id: 5,
      answer: 0,
      question: 'The best language to start learning is?',
      options: ['C++', 'Java', 'Dart', 'Pyson']),
  Questions(
      id: 6,
      answer: 3,
      question: 'Button with out splash effect',
      options: [
        'MaterialButton',
        'IconButton',
        'TextButton',
        'GestureDetector'
      ]),
  Questions(
      id: 7,
      answer: 2,
      question: 'Firebase is',
      options: ['Free service', 'Not free', 'Limited', 'None a bove is true']),
  Questions(
      id: 8,
      answer: 2,
      question: 'Widget dont take more than one child',
      options: ['Column', 'Row', 'Container', 'Stack']),
  Questions(
      id: 9,
      answer: 0,
      question: 'Widget use for input',
      options: ['TextFormField', 'Divider', 'SizedBox', 'ListTile']),
];
